support.wix.com 2009-06-13

# Wix.com:Privacy policy - Wix.com

### From Wix.com

1\. **General Principles**   

We built Wix.com to enable you to create and share web based content with your friends and people around you. We understand you may not want everyone to have access to your hosted at Wix.com; that is why we give you control of your personal content. Our default privacy settings limit the display of your content only to parties you choose to share it with. Wix.com helps you share content with your friends and people around you. You choose what content you make available to the general users of Wix.com, and you have the ability to control the users with whom you share the content you form, through the settings made during the process of publishing such content. 

Wix.com is based on the accumulation of user provided and/or formed content and there is an increasing amount of content being made available for Wix.com users. Wix.com sees it as its goal to help its users have as much content as possible available for their use while retaining each users privacy. 

**2\. Acceptance**  
,you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy statement covers any and all actions on the www.Wix.com website. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact our privacy staff at privacy@Wix.com. 

**3\. Collection and Providence of Information and Content**   

When you visit Wix.com you provide us with two types of information: limited personal information and content you knowingly choose to disclose and/or post on the Wix.com[website.](http://www.wix.com/ "http://www.wix.com")

When you register with Wix.com, you provide us with certain personal information, such as your name and your email address. 

When you enter Wix.com, we collect your browser type and IP address. This information is gathered for all Wix.com visitors. In addition, we store certain information from your browser using "cookies." A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. By default, we use a persistent cookie that stores your login ID and password to make it easier for you to login when you come back to Wix.com. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser if you want to disable this convenience feature. 

You post User Content (as defined in the Wix.com Terms of Use) on the Site at your own risk. Although we allow you to set privacy options that limit access to your personal content, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot control the actions of other Users with whom you may choose to share your pages and content. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that User Content you post on the Site will not be viewed (or even harmed) by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of User Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other Users have copied or stored your User Content. 

**4\. Sharing Your Content with Third Parties**   

Wix.com provides, as a main service, the ability of sharing created content with others friends and people in your networks while providing you with privacy settings that restrict other users from viewing and/or accessing your content without your consent. We allow you to choose the content you wish to provide to friends and networks through Wix.com and the manner in which you choose to share it. 

We may provide information and/or personal user content to service providers to help us provide the services we offer. Specifically, we may use third parties to facilitate our business, such as to host the service at a co-location facility for servers, to send out email updates about Wix.com, to remove repetitive information from our user lists, to process payments for products or services. In connection with these business operations, our service providers may have access to your personal information and/or content for use for a limited time in connection with these business activities. 

We occasionally provide demonstrations of user created content that allow non-users a glimpse into the Wix.com world. Such content is provided in a form which protects your content from any unauthorized editing and/or changing. 

We may be required to disclose user information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, or in compliance with applicable laws. We do not reveal information until we have a good faith belief that an information request by law enforcement or private litigants meets applicable legal standards. Additionally, we may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law, to protect our interests or property, to prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through the Wix.com service or using the Wix.com name, or to prevent imminent bodily harm. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents or government agencies. 

We may offer or provide services jointly with other companies on Wix.com. You can tell when another company is involved in the providence of such service on Wix.com, and we may share customer information with such third party in connection with your use of such service. 

Like many other websites that interact with third party sites, we may receive some information even if you are logged out from Wix.com, or that pertains to non-Wix.com users, from those sites in conjunction with the technical operation of our system. In cases where Wix.com receives information on users that are not logged in, or on non-Wix.com users, we do not attempt to associate it with individual Wix.com accounts and will discard it. 

In any case in which the ownership of Wix.com's business shall change, your user information may be transferred to the new owner so the service can continue operations. In any such transfer of information, your user information would remain subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy. 

When you use Wix.com, certain information you post or share with third parties (e.g., a friend or someone in your network), such as personal information, comments, messages, photos, videos or other information, may be shared with other users in accordance with the privacy settings you select. All such sharing of information is done at your own risk. 

**5\. Links Wix.com may contain links to other websites**.   

We are of course not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by Wix.com or posted on the Wix.com website. 

**6\. Third Party Advertising**  

Advertisements that appear on Wix.com are sometimes delivered (or "served") directly to users by third party advertisers. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. These third party advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and "web beacons" (also known as "1x1 gifs") to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. In this way, they may compile information about where individuals using your computer or browser saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. Wix.com does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your contact information stored on Wix.com unless you choose to share it with them. 

This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by Wix.com and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its advertisers. 

**7\. Changing or Removing Content**

Access and control over personal content on Wix.com is possible through the content editing tools. Wix.com users may modify or delete any of their personal content at any time by logging into their account. Any such changes will be updated immediately. Users who wish to deactivate their Wix.com account may do so on the My Account page. Removed information may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time but will not be generally available to users of Wix.com. 

**8\. Security**

Wix.com takes appropriate precautions to protect our users' information and content. We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards which protect your account information and uploaded content. Because email and instant messaging are not recognized as secure communications, we request that you not send private information or data to us by email or instant messaging services. If you have any questions regarding the security of Wix.com Website, please contact us at privacy@Wix.com.com. 

**9\. Terms of Use, Notices and Revisions** Your use of Wix.com, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as our General Terms of Use and all of its general provisions including warranty disclaimer, limitation of liability, indemnity and choice of law. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy and/or our General Terms of Use at any time. Any and all changes and/or clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on this site. You must refer to this policy on an ongoing basis and preferably before each use of the website so that you understand our current privacy policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and to any of your account. 

**10\. Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us at privacy@Wix.com.com. You may also contact us by mail at 115 HaChashmonaim St. Tel Aviv, Israel.
